

# **Atahan Koç**

Computer Engineer

#### Contact me:

Cep: 05426912608

E-posta: koccata@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://bit.ly/37TcCSZ

Adres: İstanbul / Türkiye

Github:

https://github.com/AtahanKocc

Dribbble:

https://dribbble.com/AtahanKoc

### **Personal Profile**

I am a graduate of Computer Engineering from Istanbul Medipol University. I am a person who likes to learn and improve himself. I have had the opportunity to experience many technologies so far. Outside of software, I like watching movies and playing video games.

# **Experiences**

Software Developer Geovision Group January 2023 - Present

Software Developer

Technix Technology
June 2022 - August 2022

Freelance Software Developer Fiverr & Upwork March 2022 - August 2022

Back-end Developer

Nabi Bilgi Teknolojileri September 2020 - October 2020

### **Educational Background**

**Istanbul Medipol University** 

# Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

September 2017- October 2022 Activities and Communities: IEEE | GDSC Medipol Uni.

Projects made during the university;

- Bookstore Application Data Structures
- Mini Bank Management System C
- University Website Project Web programming
- Blood Donation System Databases
- Student Clubs Application Software Eng.
- Classifieds App Application For Mobile Devices (Flutter)
- Emotion Recognition For AI Assisted Student Counseling (Engineering Project)

# **Anadolu University**

Business management and administration

2019-2023

### **Professional Skills**

Programming Languages:

Javascript, ReactJs C#, ASP.NET, ASP.NET MVC, Entity Framework, LINQ. Python, CSS.

Databases:

Microsoft SQL Server, MySQL, PostgreSQL.

### **Certificates**

2021 - Introduction to Machine Learning | Global AI Hub

2021 - Artificial Intelligence & Machine Learning | Google DSC Medipol University

2021 - Mobile Development | Google DSC Medipol University

2021 - Web Development | Google DSC Medipol University

2021 - Blockchain | Google DSC Medipol University

2019 - Microsoft Yazılım Uzmanlığı Kursu| Smartpro eğitim akademisi

### References

Bülent Nahırcı Software Specialist Geovision Group 05448151999